<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Grove_analog Io_3v3 Io_5v Plat_duino Plat_linkit on A test config to generate mkdocs.yml frontmatter using Hugo&#39;s templating engine</title>
    <link>http://wiki.seeed.cc/tags/grove_analog-io_3v3-io_5v-plat_duino-plat_linkit/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Grove_analog Io_3v3 Io_5v Plat_duino Plat_linkit on A test config to generate mkdocs.yml frontmatter using Hugo&#39;s templating engine</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    
	<atom:link href="http://wiki.seeed.cc/tags/grove_analog-io_3v3-io_5v-plat_duino-plat_linkit/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Grove - EMG Detector</title>
      <link>http://wiki.seeed.cc/grove-emg_detector/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://wiki.seeed.cc/grove-emg_detector/</guid>
      <description>EMG detector is a bridge connects human body and electrical, the sensor gathers small muscle signal then process with 2th amplify and filter, the output signal can be recognized by Arduino. You can add this signal into your control system.
Note
The sensor cannot be used for medical purposes.  In standby mode, the output voltage is 1.5V. When detect muscle active, the output signal rise up, the maximum voltage is 3.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Grove - High Temperature Sensor</title>
      <link>http://wiki.seeed.cc/grove-high_temperature_sensor/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://wiki.seeed.cc/grove-high_temperature_sensor/</guid>
      <description>Thermocouples are very sensitive devices. It requires a good amplifier with cold-junction compensation. The Grove - High Temperatire Sensor uses a K-Type themocouple and a thermocouple amplifier that measures ambient temperature using thermistor for cold-junction compensation. The detectable range of this Sensor is -50-600°C , and the accuracy is ±(2.0% + 2°C)

Specifications  Voltage：3.3 ~ 5V Max power rating at 25℃ ：300mW Operating temperature range：-40 ~ +125 ℃ The temperature measurement range is (-50 ~ +600℃) Amplifier output voltage range (0 ~ 3.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Grove - Luminance Sensor</title>
      <link>http://wiki.seeed.cc/grove-luminance_sensor/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://wiki.seeed.cc/grove-luminance_sensor/</guid>
      <description>Grove - Luminance Sensor detects the intensity of the ambient light on a surface area. It uses APDS-9002 analog output ambient light photo sensor. This has responsivity closer to human eye.
This Luminance Sensor can be used in application which requires automatic light adjustment in residential or commercial lighting.

Specifications    Parameter Value     Vcc 2.4V ~ 5.5V   Linear output range 0.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Grove - UV Sensor</title>
      <link>http://wiki.seeed.cc/grove-uv_sensor/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://wiki.seeed.cc/grove-uv_sensor/</guid>
      <description>The Grove – UV Sensor is used for detecting the intensity of incident ultraviolet(UV) radiation. This form of electromagnetic radiation has shorter wavelengths than visible radiation. The Grove - UV Sensor is based on the sensor GUVA-S12D which has a wide spectral range of 200nm-400nm. The module outputs electrical signal which varies with the UV intensity, which gives your suggestion if it is a good idea to beach today.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>