<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Grove_analog Io_5v Plat_duino on A test config to generate mkdocs.yml frontmatter using Hugo&#39;s templating engine</title>
    <link>http://wiki.seeed.cc/tags/grove_analog-io_5v-plat_duino/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Grove_analog Io_5v Plat_duino on A test config to generate mkdocs.yml frontmatter using Hugo&#39;s templating engine</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    
	<atom:link href="http://wiki.seeed.cc/tags/grove_analog-io_5v-plat_duino/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Grove - Alcohol Sensor</title>
      <link>http://wiki.seeed.cc/grove-alcohol_sensor/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://wiki.seeed.cc/grove-alcohol_sensor/</guid>
      <description>Grove - Alcohol Sensor is a complete alcohol sensor module for Arduino or Seeeduino. It is built with MQ303A semiconductor alcohol sensor. It has good sensitivity and fast response to alcohol. It is suitable for making Breathalyzer. This Grove implements all the necessary circuitry for MQ303A like power conditioning and heater power supply. This sensor outputs a voltage inversely proportional to the alcohol concentration in air.

Note
The sensor value only reflects the approximated trend of gas concentration in a permissible error range, it DOES NOT represent the exact gas concentration.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Grove - Gas Sensor(MQ2)</title>
      <link>http://wiki.seeed.cc/grove-gas_sensor-mq2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://wiki.seeed.cc/grove-gas_sensor-mq2/</guid>
      <description>The Grove - Gas Sensor(MQ2) module is useful for gas leakage detection (home and industry). It is suitable for detecting H2, LPG, CH4, CO, Alcohol, Smoke or Propane. Due to its high sensitivity and fast response time, measurement can be taken as soon as possible. The sensitivity of the sensor can be adjusted by potentiometer.
!!!Note The sensor value only reflects the approximated trend of gas concentration in a permissible error range, it DOES NOT represent the exact gas concentration.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Grove - Gas Sensor(MQ3)</title>
      <link>http://wiki.seeed.cc/grove-gas_sensor-mq3/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://wiki.seeed.cc/grove-gas_sensor-mq3/</guid>
      <description>The Grove - Gas Sensor(MQ3) module is useful for gas leakage detection (in home and industry). It is suitable for detecting Alcohol, Benzine, CH4, Hexane, LPG, CO. Due to its high sensitivity and fast response time, measurements can be taken as soon as possible. The sensitivity of the sensor can be adjusted by using the potentiometer.
Note
The sensor value only reflects the approximated trend of gas concentration in a permissible error range, it DOES NOT represent the exact gas concentration.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Grove - Gas Sensor(MQ5)</title>
      <link>http://wiki.seeed.cc/grove-gas_sensor-mq5/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://wiki.seeed.cc/grove-gas_sensor-mq5/</guid>
      <description>The Grove - Gas Sensor(MQ5) module is useful for gas leakage detection (in home and industry). It is suitable for detecting H2, LPG, CH4, CO, Alcohol. Due to its high sensitivity and fast response time, measurements can be taken as soon as possible. The sensitivity of the sensor can be adjusted by using the potentiometer.
Note
The sensor value only reflects the approximated trend of gas concentration in a permissible error range, it DOES NOT represent the exact gas concentration.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Grove - Gas Sensor(MQ9)</title>
      <link>http://wiki.seeed.cc/grove-gas_sensor-mq9/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://wiki.seeed.cc/grove-gas_sensor-mq9/</guid>
      <description>The Grove - Gas Sensor(MQ9) module is useful for gas leakage detection (in home and industry). It is suitable for detecting LPG, CO, CH4. Due to its high sensitivity and fast response time, measurements can be taken as soon as possible. The sensitivity of the sensor can be adjusted by using the potentiometer.
Note
The sensor value only reflects the approximated trend of gas concentration in a permissible error range, it DOES NOT represent the exact gas concentration.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>