<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Io_3v3 Io_5v Plat_duino Plat_pi on A test config to generate mkdocs.yml frontmatter using Hugo&#39;s templating engine</title>
    <link>http://wiki.seeed.cc/tags/io_3v3-io_5v-plat_duino-plat_pi/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Io_3v3 Io_5v Plat_duino Plat_pi on A test config to generate mkdocs.yml frontmatter using Hugo&#39;s templating engine</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    
	<atom:link href="http://wiki.seeed.cc/tags/io_3v3-io_5v-plat_duino-plat_pi/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Grove - PIR Motion Sensor</title>
      <link>http://wiki.seeed.cc/grove-pir_motion_sensor/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://wiki.seeed.cc/grove-pir_motion_sensor/</guid>
      <description>This sensor allows you to sense motion, usually human movement in its range. Simply connect it to Grove - Base shield and program it, when anyone moves in its detecting range, the sensor will output HIGH on its SIG pin.

Features  Grove compatible interface Adjustable detecting distance Adjustable holding time  !!!Tip More details about Grove modules please refer to Grove System
Specification    Parameter Value/Range     Operating Voltage 3V–5V   Operating Current(VCC = 3V) 100uA   Operating Current(VCC = 5V) 150uA   Measuring Range 0.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Grove - Temperature and Humidity Sensor Pro</title>
      <link>http://wiki.seeed.cc/grove-temperature_and_humidity_sensor_pro/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://wiki.seeed.cc/grove-temperature_and_humidity_sensor_pro/</guid>
      <description>This is a powerful sister version of our Grove - Temperature and Humidity Sensor. It has more complete and accurate performance than the basic version. The detecting range of this sensor is 5% RH - 99% RH, and -40°C - 80°C. And its accuracy reaches up to 2% RH and 0.5°C. A professional choice for applications that have relatively strict requirements.

Specification    Item Min Norm Max Unit     VCC 3.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Grove - Ultrasonic Ranger</title>
      <link>http://wiki.seeed.cc/grove-ultrasonic_ranger/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://wiki.seeed.cc/grove-ultrasonic_ranger/</guid>
      <description>This Grove - Ultrasonic sensor is a non-contact distance measurement module which works at 40KHz, suitable for projects that require middle distance measurement.

Product Update We have made some update on this product in order to improve the power stability when working with some low-voltage main board. The update includes:
 Added an capacitance C14 Redesigned the layout to make it more tidy Compatible with 3.3V voltage system  Here we use 2 photos to show the difference:</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>