<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Grove_i2c Io_3v3 Io_5v Plat_duino Plat_linkit Plat_bbg Plat_wio on A test config to generate mkdocs.yml frontmatter using Hugo&#39;s templating engine</title>
    <link>http://wiki.seeed.cc/tags/grove_i2c-io_3v3-io_5v-plat_duino-plat_linkit-plat_bbg-plat_wio/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Grove_i2c Io_3v3 Io_5v Plat_duino Plat_linkit Plat_bbg Plat_wio on A test config to generate mkdocs.yml frontmatter using Hugo&#39;s templating engine</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    
	<atom:link href="http://wiki.seeed.cc/tags/grove_i2c-io_3v3-io_5v-plat_duino-plat_linkit-plat_bbg-plat_wio/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Grove - 3-Axis Compass V1.0</title>
      <link>http://wiki.seeed.cc/grove-3-axis_compass_v1.0/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://wiki.seeed.cc/grove-3-axis_compass_v1.0/</guid>
      <description>This 3-axis digital compass features a low field magnetic sensing multi-chip module HMC5883L, which provides up to 1° to 2° heading accuracy. HMC5883L consists of high-resolution HMC118X series magneto-resistive sensors, as well as Honeywell developed ASIC containing amplification, automatic degaussing strap drivers, offset cancellation and 12 bit ADC. With peripheral power management circuit added, this is an easy to use and reliable compass module for low cost compassing and magnetometry.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Grove - 3-Axis Digital Gyro</title>
      <link>http://wiki.seeed.cc/grove-3-axis_digital_gyro/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://wiki.seeed.cc/grove-3-axis_digital_gyro/</guid>
      <description>Grove - 3-Axis Digital Gyro module based on ITG 3200. It is the world’s first single-chip, digital-output, 3-axis MEMS motion processing gyro optimised for gaming, 3D mice, and motion-based remote control applications for Internet connected Digital TVs and Set Top Boxes. The ITG-3200 features three 16-bit analog-to-digital converters (ADCs) for digitising the gyro outputs, a user-selectable internal low-pass filter bandwidth, and a Fast-Mode I2C (400kHz) interface.

Features  Supply Voltage: 3.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Grove - Barometer Sensor (BMP180)</title>
      <link>http://wiki.seeed.cc/grove-barometer_sensor-bmp180/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://wiki.seeed.cc/grove-barometer_sensor-bmp180/</guid>
      <description>This is a Grove module for the Bosch BMP180 high-precision, low-power digital barometer. The BMP180 offers a pressure measuring range of 300 to 1100 hPa with an accuracy down to 0.02 hPa in advanced resolution mode. It’s based on piezo-resistive technology for high accuracy, ruggedness and long term stability. The chip only accepts 1.8V to 3.6V input voltage. However, with outer circuit added, this module becomes compatible with 3.3V and 5V.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>